Guide to the Gotham Inc. Records, 1967-1997 and undated RL.00468
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1973-1996 and undated, 129 boxes
  - Major Clients, 1973-1996 and undated
    - Bristol Myers, 1973-1996 and undated
      - Comtrex (continued), 1985 (Box 32)
        - 523. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5083 Hotel Manager :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 524. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 5123 Tennis Alt. :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 525. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5243 That’s all/Dept. Store rev. :30; BMCE 5255 That’s all/Dept. Store Rev. :15. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 526. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 2993 That’s all/dept. Store": 30; That’s all questions again vers. Rev. :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 527. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMAC 4073 That’s all questions new product :30. 1985 (Box 32)
        - 528. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 5103 Tennis :30; BMAC 5113 An Allergy Profile :30. 1985 (Box 32)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1985-1986 (Box 33)
        - 529. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 5-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1985 (Box 33)
        - 530. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 5053 Not One Common Cold :30. 1985 (Box 33)
        - 531. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 5-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1985 (Box 33)
        - 532. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 5123 Tennis Alt. :30; BMAC 6013 Dreaming Lady Non Introductory :30. 1985 (Box 33)
        - 533. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 6143 Larsen candid. 1986 (Box 33)
        - 534. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. Silhouette-rev.1 (old and new trk); Silhouette-rev 2 (new trk). 1986 (Box 33)
        - 535. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1986 (Box 33)
        - 536. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex C/F. BMAO 6053 Librarian. Undated (Box 33)
        - 537. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 5-30 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1986 (Box 33)
        - 538. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson.Comtrex. BMCE 8573 return/tablet rev :30; BMCE last cold/CD rev II :30; BMCE 5243 That’s all Dept. Store rev. :30. 1986 (Box 33)
        - 539. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 6123 'Dreaming Lady Introductory :30. 1986 (Box 33)
        - 540. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 6283 A/S Medicine Chest Alt. 3 :30. Undated (Box 33)
        - 541. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 6123 Dreaming Lady Introductory :30. 1986 (Box 33)
        - 542. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Cough Formula. BMAO 6013 Silhouette :30; BMAO 6013 Silhouette Alt. Vers. :30. 1986 (Box 33)
        - 543. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. BMCE 6203 Larsen Candid Rev. :30 color. 1986 (Box 33)
        - 544. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 6303 Subjective Camera Alt. :30. 1986 (Box 33)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1986-1987 (Box 34)
        - 545. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 6293 Banner :30. 1986 (Box 34)
        - 546. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 6293 Banner :30. 1986 (Box 34)
        - 547. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 6143 Dreaming Lady Non Introductory Vers. 3 :30; BMAC 6243 Dreaming Lady Introductory :30. 1986 (Box 34)
        - 548. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMCE 7355 Pam Huerter :15; BMCE 7365 Darrell Larsen Mortise :15. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 549. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 7343 Dreaming Lady Rev. Intro :30. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 550. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. BMCO 7413 Lois :30. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 551.Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 7393 Dreaming Lady :30; BMAC 7393 Dreaming Lady Alt. :30. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 552. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson.Bristol Myers. Comtrex C/F. BMAO 6053 Librarian :30. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 553. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Cough Formula. BMAO 7063 Librarian Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 554. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 7353 Dreaming Lady Rev. Non intro :30. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 555. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 6243 Lauren Candid/New Core :30; BMCE 6253 HUERTER Candid/ New Core :30. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 556. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 7345 Pam Huerter-Mortise :15; BMCE 7375 Darrell Larsen-Mortise :15. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 557. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 7355 Pam Huerter :15; BMCE 7365 Darrell Larsen Mortise :15. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 558. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 7395 Huerter rev. :15; BMCE 7405 Larsen Rev. :15. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 559. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 7403 Exocet 1B :30. 1987 (Box 34)
        - 560. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. BMAC 7343 Dreaming Lady Rev. Intro :30; BMAC 7353 Dreaming Lady Rev. non Intro :30; BMAC 7365 Dreaming Lady :15. 1987 (Box 34)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1987-1989 (Box 35)
        - 561. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Cough Formula. BMAO 7063 Librarian Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 35)
        - 562. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 7345 Pam Huerter Mortise":15; BMCE 7375 Darrell Larsen Mortise :15. 1987 (Box 35)
        - 563. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 7345 Pam Huerter Mortise":15; BMCE 7375 Darrell Larsen Mortise :15. 1987 (Box 35)
        - 564. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Cough Formula. BMAO 7063 Librarian Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 35)
        - 565. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 8593 All in one Rev. 3 :30. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 566. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 8473 Exocet rev. III :30. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 567. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. Historicals :35. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 568. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC 8453 Exocet rev. 1 :30. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 569. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 8453 All In one :08; BMCE 8443 Plus :08; BMCE Just Relieves :08. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 570. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 8493 Indispensable Person :30. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 571. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 8493 Indispensable Person :30. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 572. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S.BMAC 8453 Exocet rev. 1 :30. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 573. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 35)
        - 574. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMAO 8075 Mr Cough Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 35)
        - 575. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. BMAO Mr Cough I Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 35)
        - 576. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMAO 8075 Mr. Cough original :15; BMAO 8075 Mr. Cough II :15. Undated. (Box 35)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1989-1993 (Box 36)
        - 577. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMAO 8075 Mr Cough :15. 1989 (Box 36)
        - 578. Comtrex Liquid Gels. 7 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 36)
        - 579. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Liquid Gels. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1989 (Box 36)
        - 580. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 5 spots. See Enclosed List. 1990 (Box 36)
        - 581. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 0793 Poor Thing Rev. 2/alt :30; BMCE Poor Thing Rev. 3/alt. :15. 1990 (Box 36)
        - 582. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1990 (Box 36)
        - 583. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. BMCE 0653 Baby Vers. 1 :30; BMCE 0683 Poor Thing :30. 1990 (Box 36)
        - 584. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1990 (Box 36)
        - 585. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 36)
        - 586. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. Photographer :30; All In One Strategy :30. 1992 (Box 36)
        - 587. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. 9 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1992 (Box 36)
        - 588. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex Maximum Strength. BMCE 2253 Photographer :30. 1992 (Box 36)
        - 589. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex Maximum Strength. BMCE 3353 Roving reporter Rev. 2 :30; BMCE 3343 Director/rev.2 :30; BMCE 3363 Roving Reporter Alt. :30. 1993 (Box 36)
        - 590. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 3353 Roving reporter Rev. 2 :30 ABC/NBC; BMCE 3343 Director/rev.2 :30; BMCE 3363 Roving Reporter Alt. :30 CBS. 1993 (Box 36)
        - 591. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 3343 Director rev.2 :30; BMCE Roving Reporter rev.2 :30. 1993 (Box 36)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1993-1995 (Box 37)
        - 592. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex Maximum Strength. BMCE 3293 Coach :30. 1993 (Box 37)
        - 593. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Comtrex. 4-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1993 (Box 37)
        - 594. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 3343 Director Rev. 2 :30; BMCE 3353 Roving/rev. 2 :30. 1993 (Box 37)
        - 595. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 2233 Film Actress A :30; BMCE 2533 Film Actress w/non-drowsy teg B :30; BMCE 2523 Film Actress w/day/night Tag B :30. 1993 (Box 37)
        - 596. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 3343 Director Rev. 2 :30; BMCE 3363 Roving Reporter Alt. :30. 1993 (Box 37)
        - 597. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 3343 Director Rev. 2 :30; BMCE 3353 Roving Reporter Rev. 2 :30; BMCE 3363 Roving Reporter Alt. :30. 1993 (Box 37)
        - 598. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMTQ 2513 Film Actress w/Flu Tag B :30. 1993 (Box 37)
        - 599. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 3343 Director Rev. 2 :30; BMCE 3353 Roving Reporter Rev. 2 :30; BMCE 3363 Roving Reporter Alt. :30. 1993 (Box 37)
        - 600. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 4315 D.J. Rev.2 :15; BMCE 4393 D.J. Old Core :30. 1994 (Box 37)
        - 601. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 4425 D.J. Rev :15. 1994 (Box 37)
        - 602. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 4393 D.J. old core :30. 1994 (Box 37)
        - 603. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 4425 D.J. Rev. Full Version :15. 1994 (Box 37)
        - 604. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 4315 DJ Alt. :15; BMCE 4315 DJ :15; BMCE 4393 DJ old core :30. 1994 (Box 37)
        - 605. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 4393 DJ old core :30. 1994 (Box 37)
        - 606. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. DJ :30; DJ rev. :15. 1994 (Box 37)
        - 607. Gotham Inc. Bristol Myers Squibb. BMCE 5485 Medicine Chest/Spill :15. 1995 (Box 37)
      - Comtrex (continued), 1995-1996 and Undated (Box 38)
        - 608. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Comtrex Nighttime. BMKN 1033 Comtrex Nighttime :30; BMKN 1021 Introducing ID :10. 1981 (Box 38)
        - 609. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex Historical Reel, 1976-1990. See Enclosed List. 1976-1990 (Box 38)
        - 610. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Comtrex A/S. BMAC Tennis :30. Undated (Box 38)
        - 611. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 4-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 38)
        - 612. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9113 I Almost Forgot :30. Undated (Box 38)
        - 613. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9113 I Almost Forgot :30. Undated (Box 38)
        - 614. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9366 Harper Rev. :60. Undated (Box 38)
        - 615. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. BMCE 9026 Harper/Candid :60. Undated (Box 38)
        - 616. Bristol Myers. Comtrex. 5-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 38)
        - 617. Gotham Inc. Comtrex Deep Chest Cold. BMCD 6005 Medicine Chest/Deep Chest New :15. 1996 (Box 38)
        - 618. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 4433 DJ Vers. A :30. 1995 (Box 38)
        - 619. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 4433 DJ Vers. A :30. 1995 (Box 38)
        - 620. Gotham Inc. Bristol Myers Squibb. Comtrex. BMCE 5485 Medicine Chest/Spill :15. 1995 (Box 38)
      - Excedrin, 1980, 1992 (Box 39)
        - 621. Bristol Myers. Excedrin PM. BMEP 0143 Travel Agent II :30. Undated (Box 39)
        - 622. Daniel & Charles. Daniel & Charles. Excedrin PM. 1 out of 3 :30. 1980 (Box 39)
        - 623. Daniel & Charles. Excedrin PM. BMEP 0143 Digital/BW Rev. 1980 (Box 39)
        - 624. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Excedrin PM. BMEP 0203 Conference Room Rev :30. 1980 (Box 39)
        - 625. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Excedrin. XYLC 2213 Pacing w/out Silhouette :30. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 626. Excedrin. XYLC 2193 Class Picture/Adult old VO, 3rd vers. Sent Via Satellite. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 627. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2053 Roller coaster/Man Rev. :30. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 628. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Excedrin. 4-30 sec spots. See Enclosed List. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 629. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2093 Roller coaster/Man Rev. :30. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 630. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2143 Roller coaster/Man/Super :30. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 631. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Excedrin Dual. XYLC 2253 Roller coaster :30; XYLC 2263 Job Interview :30. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 632. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2093 Roller coaster/Man Rev. :30. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 633. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2053 Roller coaster/Man Rev. :30. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 634. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. XYLC 2183 Class Picture/DS :30. 1992 (Box 39)
        - 635. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2075 Roller coaster/Man Rev. :15; BMEW 2095 Roller coaster/Women Rev. :15. 1992 (Box 39)
      - Excedrin (continued), 1992-1993 (Box 40)
        - 636. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. XYLC 2213 Faces :30. 1992 (Box 40)
        - 637. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2143 Roller coaster/Man/Super :30. 1992 (Box 40)
        - 638. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2143 Roller coaster/Man/Super :30. 1992 (Box 40)
        - 639. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. 4-30 sec spots. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 640. Bozell Inc. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. NFA counter Rev. :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 641. Bozell Inc. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. NFA Excedrinally Fast rev. :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 642. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. XYLC 3523 Pacing AF vers. 2 :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 643. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. XYLC 3513 Pacing Rev. :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 644. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 3183 Roller coaster/Man/Super R2 :30; BMEW 3193 Roller coaster/women/Super R2 :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 645. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. XYLC 3493 Survey AF :32 :22. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 646. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2153 Roller coaster/Women/Super :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 647. Bristol Myers Squibb. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 2153 Roller coaster/Women/Super :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 648. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin Dual. BMEW 3183 Roller coaster/Man/Super R2 :30; BMEW 3193 Roller coaster/Women/Super R2 :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 649. Bozell Inc. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. NFA Excedrin Beat Tylenol :30. 1993 (Box 40)
        - 650. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Excedrin. XYLC 3513 Pacing Rev. :30. 1993 (Box 40)
      - Keri Lotion, 1983-1986 (Box 41)
        - 651. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 3071 Keri is so Very/ID :10. 1983 (Box 41)
        - 652. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 3023 Keri is so Very :30. 1983 (Box 41)
        - 653. Laurence Charles Free. Westwood Pharmaceuticals. Keri Lotion. BMKL 3033 Skin Analysis; BMKL 3023 Keri is so Very; BMKL 3013 It's different from others. 1983 (Box 41)
        - 654. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 3023 Keri is so Very :30. 1983 (Box 41)
        - 655. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 3071 Keri is so Very/ID :10. 1983 (Box 41)
        - 656. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. BMKL 3013 It's different from others; BMKL 3023 Keri is so Very; BMKL 3033 Skin Analysis :30 Each. 1984 (Box 41)
        - 657. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 4073 Keri is so Very/Alpha Keri Tag :30. 1984 (Box 41)
        - 658. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 3013 It's different from others; BMKL 3023 Keri is so Very; BMKL 3033 Skin Analysis :30 Each Animatics. 1984 (Box 41)
        - 659. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 5105 Keri is so Very/Pool out Photographer :15; BMKL 5135 Keri is so Very/Pool out Dance :15; BMAE 5095 Alpha Keri :15. 1985 (Box 41)
        - 660. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 5105 Keri is so Very/Pool out Photographer :15; BMKL 5135 Keri is so Very/Pool out Dance :15; BMAE 5095 Alpha Keri :15. 1985 (Box 41)
        - 661. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 4043 Keri is so Very Alpha Keri-Bath :30; BMKL 4053 Keri is so very Alpha Keri-Shower :30. 1984 (Box 41)
        - 662. Laurence Charles Free. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 5083 Keri is so very/coupon :30. 1985 (Box 41)
        - 663. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 6193 I switched (tag change) :30. 1986 (Box 41)
        - 664. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Westwood Pharmaceuticals. Keri Lotion. BMKL 6152 Switched/Alpha Keri-Shower :22/8; BMKL 6165 Switched :15. 1986 (Box 41)
        - 665. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 6215 I switched/Double Tag :15. 1986 (Box 41)
        - 666. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKL 6193 I switched :30; BMKL 6215 Double Tag :15. 1986 (Box 41)
        - 667. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKL 6223 I switched (Tag Change) :30. 1986 (Box 41)
      - Keri Lotion (continued), 1987-1991 (Box 42)
        - 668. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 7075 I Switched-Double Tag :15. 1987 (Box 42)
        - 669. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Alpha Keri Lotion. BMAE 7113 Women in Pool :30; BMAE 7095 Women In Pool :15. 1987 (Box 42)
        - 670. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Alpha Keri Lotion. BMAE 7113 Women in Pool :30; BMAE 7095 Women In Pool :15. 1987 (Box 42)
        - 671. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Westwood Pharmaceuticals. Alpha Keri Lotion. BMAE 7013 Women in Pool :30. 1987 (Box 42)
        - 672. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Keri. Pre sun Summer Skin Savers. BMPJ 7033 :30 (Non-retail); BMPJ 7043 :30 (retail). 1987 (Box 42)
        - 673. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Keri. Pre sun Bleach. BMPJ 6025 :15 CBS vers. 1986 (Box 42)
        - 674. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Pre sun Summer Skin Savers. BMPJ 7033 :30 (Non-retail); BMPJ 7043 :30 (retail). 1987 (Box 42)
        - 675. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Alpha Keri Lotion. BMAE 7113 women in pool :30; BMAE 7095 Women In Pool :15. 1987 (Box 42)
        - 676. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Alpha Keri Lotion. BMAE 7113 women in pool :30; BMAE 7095 Women In Pool :15. 1988 (Box 42)
        - 677. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Keri Lotion. BMKL 9243 Nursery :30. 1989 (Box 42)
        - 678. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKL 0195 Keri is so Very Different rev. 3 Alt. :30. 1990 (Box 42)
        - 679. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKL 0233 Group of Women rev. :30. 1990 (Box 42)
        - 680. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. BMKL 9263 Keri Lotion-Beautiful Baby :330; BMKL 9275 Keri Lotion-Beautiful Baby :15. 1990 (Box 42)
        - 681. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 0243 Flourish Nourish Rev. Ver. 2 :30. 1990 (Box 42)
        - 682. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMkk 1373 Inside Outside rev. :30; BMKK 1385 Inside Outside Rev. :15. 1991 (Box 42)
        - 683. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 1373 Inside Outside rev. :30; BMKK 1385 Inside Outside Rev. :15. 1991 (Box 42)
        - 684. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 1373 Inside Outside rev. :30; BMKK 1385 Inside Outside Rev. :15. 1991 (Box 42)
      - Keri Lotion (continued), 1991-1994 (Box 43)
        - 685. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 1323 Diet :30. 1991 (Box 43)
        - 686. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 1373 Inside Outside Rev. :30; BMKK 1385 Inside Outside Rev. :15. 1991 (Box 43)
        - 687. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Lotion. BMKL 3023 Keri Is So Very :30. 1991 (Box 43)
        - 688. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 1373 Inside Outside Rev. :30; BMKK 1385 Inside Outside Rev. :15. 1991 (Box 43)
        - 689. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 0253 Flourish Nourish :30; BMKK 0263 Group of Women :30. 1991 (Box 43)
        - 690. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 1503 Fragrance Free Tag Rev. 2 :30. 1992 (Box 43)
        - 691. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri. BMWK 2053 Inside Outside w/KC10 :30. 1992 (Box 43)
        - 692. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. BMKK 2523 Inside Outside/VIT E Tag :30. 1992 (Box 43)
        - 693. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Keri Silky Smooth. Inside Outside Moisture BMKK 3613 :30; BMKK 3625 :15. 1993 (Box 43)